<resources>
    <string name="app_name">purpleivvy</string>
    <string name="title">Artwork Title</string>
    <string name="short_description">Description of the Artwork</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Previous</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="front_page_icon">Front page icon</string>
    <string name="front_page_title">\@purpleivvy</string>
    <string name="front_page_button_text">Enter, Immerse, Explore</string>
    <string name="front_page_bg_content_desc">Background image of the start page</string>
    <string name="front_page_heading">Embark on an Artistic Adventure\!</string>

    <string name="art1_title">Wanderer</string>
    <string name="art1_description">The Wanderer in Genshin Impact is a courageous and determined
        protagonist exploring the vibrant realm of Teyvat.</string>
    <string name="art1_imageContentDescription">Wanderer from Genshin Impact game</string>

    <string name="art2_title">Makima</string>
    <string name="art2_description">Makima is a compelling character from the manga series
        "Chainsaw Man." She possesses a mysterious and manipulative nature as the leader of
        Public Safety Devil Hunters.</string>
    <string name="art2_imageContentDescription">Makima from the series Chainsaw Man</string>

    <string name="art3_title">A Dragon</string>
    <string name="art3_description">This drawing from Twenty One Pilots is a symbolic
        representation of resilience and overcoming inner struggles. It embodies the band\'s
        message of facing personal demons and transforming them into sources of strength.</string>
    <string name="art3_imageContentDescription">Dragon Icon from Twenty One Pilots</string>

    <string name="art4_title">An Original Character</string>
    <string name="art4_description">With a determined gaze, she takes hold of the crimson ribbon,
        a symbol of constraints. As her blade slices through it, she liberates herself, embracing
        newfound freedom.</string>
    <string name="art4_imageContentDescription">A girl cutting a red ribbon</string>

    <string name="art5_title">Skyscraper Lovebirds</string>
    <string name="art5_description">Perched atop the skyscraper\'s pinnacle, their legs dangle
        fearlessly, defying gravity. Amidst the urban chaos, they find solace in each other\'s
        presence, their intertwined souls symbolizing an unbreakable bond fueled by
        boundless love.</string>
    <string name="art5_imageContentDescription">Two lovers sitting on the top of a
        skyscraper</string>

    <string name="art6_title">Rooted Serenity: Blooming Love</string>
    <string name="art6_description">Nature\'s embrace, a lady blooms adorned with vibrant foliage,
        her heart aglow with azure light, symbolizing deep connection and inner growth.</string>
    <string name="art6_imageContentDescription">A young lady covered with leaves and
        flowers.</string>

    <string name="art7_title">Tighnari</string>
    <string name="art7_description">Tighnari - A young researcher well-versed in botany who
        currently serves as a Forest Watcher in Avidya Forest. He is a straight shooter with
        a warm heart - and a dab hand at guiding even the dullest of pupils.</string>
    <string name="art7_imageContentDescription">Tighnari from Genshin Impact</string>

    <string name="art8_title">Cometary Symphony</string>
    <string name="art8_description">Ethereal comets intertwine in a mesmerizing artwork,
        capturing the fleeting beauty and destined encounters of the celestial tapestry.</string>
    <string name="art8_imageContentDescription">Two Comets in sky from the anime "Your
        Name"</string>

    <string name="art9_title">Brendon Urie: The Melodic Monarch</string>
    <string name="art9_description">Brendon from Panic at the Disco wears a majestic crown,
        embodying his musical reign. The band\'s logo gleams as a butterfly flutters nearby,
        symbolizing metamorphosis and the transformative artistry of the band.</string>
    <string name="art9_imageContentDescription">Brendon from Panic At The Disco</string>

    <string name="art10_title">Suffocating Shadows</string>
    <string name="art10_description">In a moment of vulnerability, the young girl\'s desperate
        cry echoes through the closing gate. As darkness engulfs her, a slender beam of light
        peeks through the slightly ajar door, symbolizing hope\'s delicate persistence amidst
        confinement.</string>
    <string name="art10_imageContentDescription">A girl peeking behind the closing door</string>

    <string name="art11_title">Blossoming Reflections</string>
    <string name="art11_description">Violet Evergarden amidst blossoms, exudes depth and
        vulnerability. Her enigmatic gaze symbolizes the delicate balance between strength and
        longing, amidst the ethereal beauty of petals.</string>
    <string name="art11_imageContentDescription">MC from the anime Violet Evergarden</string>

    <string name="art12_title">Lost Whispers</string>
    <string name="art12_description">In the heart of a lush forest, the protagonist of
        "Ousama Ranking" lies gently embraced by nature\'s embrace. Through vulnerability and
        introspection, they find solace and the seeds of resilience, ready to bloom.</string>
    <string name="art12_imageContentDescription">MC from the anime Ousama Ranking</string>

    <string name="art13_title">Microcosmic Oasis</string>
    <string name="art13_description">Within the cup\'s depths, a miniature world unfolds—a serene
        pond brimming with life. The lotus blossoms symbolize resilience, reminding us that
        even within confined spaces, beauty and tranquility can flourish.</string>
    <string name="art13_imageContentDescription">A cup which contains a small pond</string>

    <string name="art14_title">Illuminated Charm of Gojo</string>
    <string name="art14_description">Gojo from Jujutsu Kaisen wears circular black glasses,
        his infectious smile illuminated by the warm embrace of sunlight. The contrasting
        hues reflect his enigmatic charisma and the brilliance he brings to the world.</string>
    <string name="art14_imageContentDescription">Gojo Satoru from JJK Anime</string>

    <string name="art15_title">TØP</string>
    <string name="art15_description">Twenty One Pilots depicted in this vibrant art piece,
        contrasting their introspective lyrics with a burst of vivid colors. Their music, like a
        kaleidoscope, blends diverse emotions into a harmonious symphony.</string>
    <string name="art15_imageContentDescription">Twenty One Pilots</string>

    <string name="art16_title">Whimsical Abode from Spirited Away</string>
    <string name="art16_description">A whimsical, cartoon-style portrayal of a traditional Japanese
        home from "Spirited Away," encapsulating the enchanting magic of Studio
        Ghibli\'s imaginative realm.</string>
    <string name="art16_imageContentDescription">A traditional Japanese home from "Spirited
        Away"</string>

    <string name="art17_title">Nail-Kissed Roses</string>
    <string name="art17_description">Nobara from Jujutsu Kaisen, wielding lethal precision,
        merges beauty and danger. Delicate roses adorn her face, epitomizing a captivating
        blend of fury and grace.</string>
    <string name="art17_imageContentDescription">Nobara from Jujutsu Kaisen</string>
</resources>